

# **MOCH SEHAN RESTU P**

## Sistem Informasi

083892136024

@mochsehan r

mochsehanrestu@gmail.com kp.cibuah Ds.panyadap Kec.solokan jeruk Kab. bandung

# ABOUT ME

I am a 22 year old information system student at the Indonesian Computer University born in Bandung

have an interest in learning new things and I have experience in the field of information systems. I am an honest, patient, diligent, and hardworking person.

### EXPERIENCE

• 2020 - present Staff Divisi minbakom Himpunan mahasiswa

In my association, I was the chief executive of Simicup, a cup information system that only held 2 sports, namely badminton and futsal

• Juni 2022 - agustus 2022

Tim sponsorship Kedai reka

Participate in helping to find sponsorship for shop design seminars and design funding and MOU collaborations with partners.

2017 - 2020

**SMAN 2 Pandeglang** 

**EDUCATION** 

Jurusan IPS

**2020 - present** 

Universitas komputer indonesia

Sistem informasi (GPA: 3.21)

# **KEAHLIAN**

- Teamwork
- Figma
- Leadership
- Vs Code
- Canva
- Critical Thinking
- Flimora